<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaleidoscope</title>
    <link>https://kaleidoscope.keyboard.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kaleidoscope</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 08:33:45 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kaleidoscope.keyboard.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Porting to a new keyboard</title>
      <link>https://kaleidoscope.keyboard.io/articles/hardware-porting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 08:33:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaleidoscope.keyboard.io/articles/hardware-porting/</guid>
      <description>The goal of this guide is to show you how to add support for a new keyboard to Kaleidoscope. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t go further than that: this guide doesn&amp;rsquo;t help you maintain an hardware plugin in an external repository, nor does it document everything that makes for a good pull request for a keyboard. It goes far enough to have it working, in a quick and dirty way, anything further than that will be the topic of another guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>https://kaleidoscope.keyboard.io/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaleidoscope.keyboard.io/impressum/</guid>
      <description>This is the website of the Kaleidoscope firmware, created and maintained by Keyboardio and contributors. You can find the sources on GitHub. All content is released under the terms of CC-BY-SA 4.0, unless stated otherwise.
Logo by Simon-Claudius Wystrach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboards</title>
      <link>https://kaleidoscope.keyboard.io/keyboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaleidoscope.keyboard.io/keyboards/</guid>
      <description>Keyboards powered by Kaleidoscope These keyboards use Kaleidoscope as their official and default firmware.
Keyboardio Model01 Dygma Raise Keyboards supported by Kaleidoscope Apart from the keyboards that ship with Kaleidoscope as their official firmware, others are supported as well, with Kaleidoscope as an alternative firmware for them.
Atreus ErgoDox    The firmware supports any keyboard wired like the original ErgoDox, including the ErgoDox EZ. We do not support additional features of the EZ (such as Shine or Glow) yet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>